{"data":[{"question":"I _____ on that typerwriter before.","a":"never type","b":"am never typed","c":"never typed","d":"had never typed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past \n+ Unspecific expressions such as: ever, never, once, many times, several times, before, so far, already, yet... \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...) ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She was nervous because she _______ before.","a":"has never driven","b":"had driven never","c":"had never driven","d":"had never drove","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Tense:\n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past. \nNever drived before-> nervous\n+ Unspecific expressions such as: ever, never, once, many times, several times, before, so far, already, yet...\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ Past Participle + (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He was no longer running his shop. He _____it.","a":"had sold","b":"has sell","c":"had sell","d":"has sold","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: - Past Perfect Tense:\n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\nAction \"Sell the shop\" lead to action \"no longer run it\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"When I arrived everything _____ a lot.","a":"has changed","b":"had changed","c":"changed","d":"is changed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense:\n+ Action \"changed\" happen before action \"arrived\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Now there were three cinemas. They _______ another one.","a":"have opened","b":"have open","c":"had opened","d":"had open","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past: \n+ Action \"opened\" lead to \"there were three cinema\" \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I went to bed early. I _____ to bed so early.","a":"had never gone","b":"had never been","c":"has never gone","d":"am never gone","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...) ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I found that my old friend _____ again.","a":"had got married","b":"has got married","c":"has marry","d":"had got marry","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"married\" happened before action \"found\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He loved the zoo. He _____ wild animals before","a":"had never seen","b":"has never seen","c":"never saw","d":"is never seen","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He was nervous because he _____ before.","a":"has never worked","b":"has never work","c":"had never worked","d":"has worked never","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Part Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past: \nNever worked- nervous \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...) ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The place was very quiet. Everybody _______ to bed.","a":"has gone","b":"is going","c":"had gone","d":"was going","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Part Perfect tense:\n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\nAction \"went to bed\" lead to \"quite place\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}